Welcome back to APUS history in under 3
minutes. No time for intros, let's get
into it. This video serves as a
continuation of the things talked about
in my topic 2.3 video. So, please make
sure to watch that first before watching
this video. So, we already know that
there was a shortage of indentured
servants, and therefore the British
started participating in the African
slave trade. The system that African
slaves were employed under the Spanish
was called asiento, but in English
colonies they were employed under a
separate system known as chattel
slavery, where slaves were treated as
property and not people. These African
slaves worked heavily in the Chesapeake
Bay and Southern Atlantic coast, but the
majority of them were in the West
Indies. As chattel slavery became
dominant, the interracial relationships
between colonists and slaves became
illegal, which made Africans only breed
with other Africans, and new laws were
put in place that their children would
automatically be slaves. I know, it's
awful. But, even with this level of
hopelessness, some Africans rebelled
with an example being the First Maroon
War. But, most that didn't rebel tried
to survive by maintaining their own
people's culture. One example of this
being the Gullah community, which
maintained African traditions such as
dancing to West African music during
their rare moments of relaxation. That's
all for this one. On the screen now are
AP style questions for this topic. Pause
now.
I'll put the answers on the screen now.
See you in the next one.